Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1991-2010; 14
  - 2002, 11
    - Religion, Religious Freedom, Religious Freedom Restoration Amendment (HJ Res 81), 2002 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Religion, Ten Commandments, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Service, Postal, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Social Security, General, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Social Security, Congressional Retirement, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - Social Security, Notch Fairness Act (HR 97 & HR 853), 2002 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - Social Security, Personal Retirement Accounts, Opinion Ballot, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - Social Security, Privatization, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - Social Security, Reform, 2002 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - Social Security, Social Security Fairness Act (HR 2638) (1 of 3), 2002 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Social Security, Social Security Fairness Act (HR 2638) (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - Social Security, Social Security Fairness Act (HR 2638) (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 323, Folder 14)
    - Social Security, Tax on Benefits, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Tax, General, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Tax, Estate Tax, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Tax, “Fair Tax: A National Sales Tax Proposal”, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Tax, “Tax Cuts: Pension Savings and Capital Losses”, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Tax, Tax Limitation Amendment, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Tax, VOTR Tax Reform Pledge, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Trade, General, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Trade, Trade Promotion Authority, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Transportation, General, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, Airline Security, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Airlines, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, Motor Carrier Fuel Cost Equity Act (HR 2161), 2002 (Box 324, Folder 13)
    - Transportation, Railroads, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 14)
    - Transportation, Robert Gray Joint-Use Airfield, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Safe Routes to School, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 16)
    - United Nations, UNFPA Funding, 2002 (Box 324, Folder 17)
    - Veterans Affairs, General (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 324, Folder 18)
    - Veterans Affairs, General (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 324, Folder 19)
    - Veterans Affairs, Benefits, 2002 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Affairs, Disabilities (HR 440), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, Concurrent Receipt (HR 303), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Affairs, Extending Tax Benefits for Combat Service in Korea (HR 3412), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, Marlin VA Update, 2002 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (1 of 21), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (2 of 21), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 7)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (3 of 21), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 8)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (4 of 21), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 9)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (5 of 21), 2002 (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (6 of 21), 2002 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (7 of 21), 2002 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (8 of 21), 2002 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (9 of 21), 2002 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (10 of 21), 2002 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (11 of 21), 2002 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (12 of 21), 2002 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (13 of 21), 2002 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (14 of 21), 2002 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (15 of 21), 2002 (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (16 of 21), 2002 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (17 of 21), 2002 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (18 of 21), 2002 (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (19 of 21), 2002 (Box 328, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (20 of 21), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Affairs, Retired Pay/Service-Connected Disability (21 of 21), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, Survivor Benefit Plan (SBP), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Affairs, Uniformed Services Former Spouses Protection Act (HR 1983), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, VA Budget FY03, 2002 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Affairs, Veterans Health Care Funding Guarantee Act (HR 5250), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Affairs, Veterans Judicial Review Improvement Act (HR 4018), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Welfare, General, 2002 (Box 329, Folder 8)
    - Welfare, Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF), 2002 (Box 329, Folder 9)
  - 2003, 12
    - General, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - General, Invitations, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - General, Thank Yous (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - General, Thank Yous (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Administrative, General, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Administrative, Information Requests, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Administrative, Interns, Pages, & Volunteers, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 7)
    - Abortion, General, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 8)
    - Abortion, Abortion Pill, 2003 (Box 330, Folder 9)
    - Abortion, Late Term Abortion (1 of 5), 2003 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Abortion, Late Term Abortion (2 of 5), 2003 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, Late Term Abortion (3 of 5), 2003 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Abortion, Late Term Abortion (4 of 5), 2003 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Abortion, Late Term Abortion (5 of 5), 2003 (Box 331, Folder 5)
    - Abortion, Legislation, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 6)
    - Abortion, Military Abortion Amendment, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, General, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 8)
    - Agriculture, Antibiotics, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 9)
    - Agriculture, Country of Origin Labeling, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, Dairy, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture, Horse Slaughter Prevention, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture, Hunting & Fishing, 2003 (Box 331, Folder 13)
    - Agriculture, Livestock, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Organic Labeling, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 2)
    - Alcohol, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 3)
    - Arts, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Banking, General, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Banking, Bankruptcy, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Banking, Bonds, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 7)
    - Banking, Fair Credit Reporting Act, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 8)
    - Banking, Real Estate, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 9)
    - Banking, Securities & Exchange Commission (SEC), 2003 (Box 332, Folder 10)
    - Budget, General, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 11)
    - Budget, Budget Resolution FY 2004, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 12)
    - Budget, Bush Economic Stimulus Package (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 332, Folder 13)
    - Budget, Bush Economic Stimulus Package (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 332, Folder 14)
    - Budget, Bush Economic Stimulus Package (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 332, Folder 15)
    - Campaign Reform, 2003 (Box 332, Folder 16)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 2003 (Box 332, Folder 17)
    - Children, General, 2003 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Children, Adoption, 2003 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Children, National Amber Alert, 2003 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Cities (Alphabetical), 2003 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights, General, 2003 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (1 of 8), 2003 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (2 of 8), 2003 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (3 of 8), 2003 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (4 of 8), 2003 (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (5 of 8), 2003 (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (6 of 8), 2003 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (7 of 8), 2003 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Civil Rights, Defense of Marriage (8 of 8), 2003 (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights, Gay Rights, 2003 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Civil Rights, Human Rights, 2003 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights, Race, 2003 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Communications, General, 2003 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (1 of 8), 2003 (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (2 of 8), 2003 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (3 of 8), 2003 (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (4 of 8), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (5 of 8), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (6 of 8), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (7 of 8), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Communications, Cursing on TV & Radio (8 of 8), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Communications, FCC & Media Diversity (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Communications, FCC & Media Diversity (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Communications, Internet, 2003 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Communications, Radio, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Communications, Telephone, General, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Communications, Telephone, Do-Not-Call List, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, General, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, Death Penalty, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, Hate Crimes, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Justice, Prisons & Prison Industries, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - Criminal Justice, Sexual & Domestic Violence, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Criminal Justice, Unborn Victims of Violence Act, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice, Victims of Crime, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Defense, General, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Defense, Anti-War Protesting, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Defense, Armed Forces & Taxes, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - Defense, Army Privatization, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - Defense, Civil Service Reform, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - Defense, Draft, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 16)
    - Defense, Education, General, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 17)
    - Defense, Education, Impact Aid, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 18)
    - Defense, Ex-Spouse Benefits, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 19)
    - Defense, Fort Hood, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 20)
    - Defense, Health Care, General, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 21)
    - Defense, Health Care, TRICARE Coverage, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 22)
    - Defense, Health Care, TRICARE for Reserves, 2003 (Box 336, Folder 23)
    - Defense, Hospital Food for Wounded Troops, 2003 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Korea Quality of Life Act, 2003 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Defense, Life Insurance, Cuthbert Report, 2003 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Lt Col. Allen B. West Interrogation (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Defense, Lt. Col. Allen B. West Interrogation (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Defense, Lt. Col. Allen B. West Interrogation (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Defense, Lt. General Boykin & Religion, 2003 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Defense, Mail to Deployed Troops, 2003 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, General, 2003 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Concurrent Receipt (1 of 5), 2003 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Concurrent Receipt (2 of 5), 2003 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Concurrent Receipt (3 of 5), 2003 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Concurrent Receipt (4 of 5), 2003 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Concurrent Receipt (5 of 5), 2003 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Keep Our Promise to America’s Military Retirees Act, 2003 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Defense, Military Retirees, Reservist Retirement, 2003 (Box 338, Folder 5)
    - Defense, Nuclear Weapons, 2003 (Box 338, Folder 6)
    - Defense, Spending & Funding, 2003 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Defense, Uniformed Services Pay Raise, 2003 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Disabilities, General, 2003 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Disabilities, Council for Exceptional Children (CEC), 2003 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Disabilities, Individuals with Disabilities Education Act (IDEA), 2003 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - Education, General, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Education, Adult Education, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Education, Afterschool Programs, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Education, Communities In Schools, Belton ISD, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Education, Communities In Schools, Copperas Cove ISD, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Education, Communities In Schools, Killeen ISD, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Education, Communities In Schools, Rogers ISD, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Education, Communities In Schools, Salado ISD, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Education, Communities In Schools, Temple ISD, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Education, Congressional Award Program, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - Education, Head Start, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Education, Higher Education, General, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - Education, Higher Education, Federal Aid & Drug Convictions, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - Education, Higher Education, Tuition, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 14)
    - Education, Homeschool, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - Education, No Child Left Behind, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 16)
    - Education, Perkins Loans, 2003 (Box 339, Folder 17)
    - Education, School Prayer, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Education, School Vouchers, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Education, Sex Education, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Education, Teachers, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Education, Title IX Change Proposal, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - Economy, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - Elections, General, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - Elections, Voting, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - Energy, General, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - Energy, Electricity, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Energy, Energy Bill, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - Energy, Enron, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Energy, Oil & Gas, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Energy, Renewable Energy, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 14)
    - Environment, General, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 15)
    - Environment, Animal Welfare, General, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 16)
    - Environment, Animal Welfare, Aquatic Life, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 17)
    - Environment, Animal Welfare, Endangered Species, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 18)
    - Environment, Anti-Environmental Riders, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 19)
    - Environment, Clean Air Act, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 20)
    - Environment, Defense Exemptions, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 21)
    - Environment, Forests, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 22)
    - Environment, Oil Drilling, Arctic National Wildlife Refuge (ANWR), 2003 (Box 340, Folder 23)
    - Environment, Oil Drilling, Off-Shore Drilling, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 24)
    - Environment, Water, General, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 25)
    - Environment, Water, Clean Water Act, 2003 (Box 340, Folder 26)
    - Flags, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Affairs, General, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Affairs, Africa, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs, Asia, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Affairs, Europe, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Affairs, Global Fund, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Affairs, Middle East, General, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Affairs, Middle East, Israel & Palestine, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Affairs, Middle East, Rachel Corrie, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Affairs, Millennium Challenge Account (MCA), 2003 (Box 341, Folder 11)
    - Gambling, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 12)
    - Government Affairs, General, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 13)
    - Government Affairs, Bush Impeachment, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 14)
    - Government Affairs, Congress, General, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 15)
    - Government Affairs, Congress, Controversial Comments, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 16)
    - Government Affairs, Congress, Pay Raise, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 17)
    - Government Affairs, Congress, Retirement, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 18)
    - Government Affairs, Democratic Party, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 19)
    - Government Affairs, English Language, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Gun Control, General, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Gun Control, Assault Weapons Ban (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Gun Control, Assault Weapons Ban (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Gun Control, Ban on Undetectable Weapons, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Gun Control, Citizens’ Self-Defense Act, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Gun Control, Concealed Weapons, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 7)
    - Gun Control, Gun Lawsuits, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 8)
    - Gun Control, Right to Bear Arms Act, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 9)
    - Health, General, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 10)
    - Health, CHIP (Children’s Health Insurance Program), 2003 (Box 342, Folder 11)
    - Health, Family Planning, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 12)
    - Health, Immunization, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 13)
    - Health, Insurance, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 14)
    - Health, Legislation, 2003 (Box 342, Folder 15)
    - Health, Medical Malpractice, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Health, Medical Research & Funding, General, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Health, Medical Research & Funding, Arthritis, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Health, Medical Research & Funding, Cancer, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Health, Medical Research & Funding, Diabetes, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Health, Medical Research & Funding, Stem Cell Research - SCNT, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Health, Medicare & Medicaid Funding Cuts, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Health, Mental Health, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Health, Nursing, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Health, Nutritional Supplements, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - Health, Prescription Drugs, General, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - Health, Prescription Drugs, Drug Importation, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - Health, Rural Health Care, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 13)
    - Homeland Security, General, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 14)
    - Homeland Security, First Responder Initiative, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 15)
    - Homeland Security, Freedom to Read Protection Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Homeland Security, Intelligence Authorization Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Homeland Security, Patriot Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Homeland Security, Security and Freedom Ensured Act (SAFE), 2003 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Homeland Security, Terrorism, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Homeland Security, Total Information Awareness, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - Homeland Security, Victory Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Housing, General, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Housing, American Dream Down Payment Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - Illegal Drugs, General, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 10)
    - Illegal Drugs, Marijuana, DEA Raids, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 11)
    - Illegal Drugs, Marijuana, Legalization, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 12)
    - Illegal Drugs, Marijuana, Medical Marijuana, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 13)
    - Illegal Drugs, RAVE & Clean Up Acts, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 14)
    - Immigration, General, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 15)
    - Immigration, Ag JOBS Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 16)
    - Immigration, Border Patrol, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 17)
    - Immigration, Foreign-Issued ID Cards, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 18)
    - Immigration, Illegal Immigration, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 19)
    - Immigration, Immigration Reduction, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 20)
    - Immigration, National Security Registration System, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 21)
    - Immigration, Permanent Partners Immigration Act, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 22)
    - Immigration, Visa, General, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 23)
    - Immigration, Visa, Lottery, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 24)
    - Interior, General, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 25)
    - Interior, National Parks, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 26)
    - Interior, Public Parks, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 27)
    - Interior, Roadways on Public Land - Udall Amendment, 2003 (Box 344, Folder 28)
    - Iraq, General (1 of 3), 2003 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Iraq, General (2 of 3), 2003 (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - Iraq, General (3 of 3), 2003 (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - Iraq, $87 Billion Supplemental Aid (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - Iraq, $87 Billion Supplemental Aid (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Iraq, Bring Troops Home, 2003 (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - Iraq, Media Coverage, 2003 (Box 345, Folder 7)
    - Iraq, Rebuilding Iraq, 2003 (Box 345, Folder 8)
    - Iraq, Related Issues, 2003 (Box 345, Folder 9)
    - Iraq, Stop Loss, 2003 (Box 345, Folder 10)
    - Iraq, Supplemental Pay, 2003 (Box 345, Folder 11)
    - Iraq, War Profiteering Prevention Act, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Iraq, Weapons of Mass Destruction Investigation, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Judicial, General, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Judicial, Class Action Reform, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Judicial, Court of Appeals Judicial Appointments, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Judicial, Federal Judges, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - Judicial, Supreme Court, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - Judicial, Tort Reform, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Labor, General, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Labor, Association Health Plans (AHPs), 2003 (Box 346, Folder 10)
    - Labor, Federal Employee Pay Raise, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 11)
    - Labor, Federal Overtime Pay Rules, 2003 (Box 346, Folder 12)
    - Labor, Minimum Wage, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Labor, Small Business, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Labor, Unemployment, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Labor, Workforce Reinvestment & Adult Education Act, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Legislation, General, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Legislation, Congressional Responsibility Act, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - Legislation, Enumerated Powers Act, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, Family Values, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 8)
    - Legislation, Multiple Issues (1 of 4), 2003 (Box 347, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, Multiple Issues (2 of 4), 2003 (Box 347, Folder 10)
    - Legislation, Multiple Issues (3 of 4), 2003 (Box 347, Folder 11)
    - Legislation, Multiple Issues (4 of 4), 2003 (Box 347, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, Obscenity Laws, 2003 (Box 347, Folder 13)
    - Media, General, 2003 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Media, Digital Media Bills, 2003 (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Media, Public Broadcasting Service (PBS), 2003 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Medicare, General, 2003 (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Medicare, Cancer Care, 2003 (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - Medicare, Medicare Bill, General, 2003 (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - Medicare, Medicare Bill, Prescription Drug Coverage (1 of 5), 2003 (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - Medicare, Medicare Bill, Prescription Drug Coverage (2 of 5), 2003 (Box 348, Folder 8)
    - Medicare, Medicare Bill, Prescription Drug Coverage (3 of 5), 2003 (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - Medicare, Medicare Bill, Prescription Drug Coverage (4 of 5), 2003 (Box 348, Folder 10)